HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005: A Finding Aid
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005
- Series II. Staff Photographs, 1940-2001
  - Subseries A. Staff, A-Z, circa 1940-circa 1994
    - Linda M. Carrigan (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 31)
    - Gregory Cascante (Harvard Business Review), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Karen Castaldi, circa 1985 (Box 31)
    - Fleur H. Cates (MBA Program), circa 1980 (Box 31)
    - Sheila C. Cavenaugh, 1991 (Box 31)
    - Helen G. Cauchon (Case Services), circa 1970 (Box 31)
    - Judith S. Chadwick (Office of the Dean), circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - William G. Chafee, circa 1965 (Box 31)
    - Balaji S. Chakravarthy (Research Associate), 1975 (Box 31)
    - Subrata N. Chakravarty (Research Assistant), circa 1971 (Box 31)
    - Richard Chapin (Office of the Dean), 1950s (Box 31)
    - John F. Chapman (Harvard Business Review), 1960s (Box 31)
    - Robert W. Chase (Alumni Relations), circa 1955 (Box 31)
    - Mary Van A. Chatfield (Baker Library), circa 1964 (Box 31)
    - Xiu Chen (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 31)
    - Rita V. Cherington (DBA Program), 1980s (Box 31)
    - Barbara Chidley, 1939 (Box 31)
    - James A. Christianson (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 31)
    - Ann M. Cichon (Executive Education), circa 1980-1994 (Box 32)
    - Mary Ellen Clapper (Baker Library), circa 1980 (Box 32)
    - Bruce H. Clark (Research Associate), circa 1986 (Box 32)
    - Donald T. Clark (Baker Library), 1940s-1960s (Box 32)
    - Jane Clark (Office of the Dean), circa 1965 (Box 32)
    - Marie T. Clark (Computer Services), circa 1975 (Box 32)
    - Robert P Clark (Executive Education), circa 1965 (Box 32)
    - James W. Clauson, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 32)
    - William J. Clements (Baker Library), ca. 1960 (Box 32)
    - Lawrence W. Clauson (Research Associate), circa 1985 (Box 32)
    - Jeffrey M. Cohn (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 32)
    - Priscilla Coit (MBA Program), circa 1970 (Box 32)
    - Rita Colella (Finance), 1995 (Box 32)
    - Eliza C. Collins (Harvard Business Review), 1970s (Box 32)
    - Edward E. Combs (Research Associate), circa 1953 (Box 32)
    - A. Phillip Connoly, Jr. (Health Services), circa 1965 (Box 32)
    - Melinda B. Conrad (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 32)
    - Warren K. Cooper (Financial Aid), circa 1967 (Box 32)
    - William K. Cooper (Research Assistant), circa 1958 (Box 32)
    - Dana W. Corsi, 1993 (Box 32)
    - Maryellen Costello (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 32)
    - Catherine A. Cotins (MBA Admissions), circa 1985 (Box 32)
    - Lillian M. Cotter (Finance), 1950s (Box 32)
    - Justine Covault (HBS Publishing), 1989 (Box 32)
    - Leslie P. Coyle Jr., (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 32)
    - Robert L. Crane (Executive Education), circa 1970 (Box 32)
    - David Croson (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 32)
    - Violette G. Crowe, 1985 (Box 32)
    - Jeff Cruikshank, circa 1987 (Box 32)
    - Romy Cullen (MBA Financial Aid), 1993 (Box 32)
    - Charlene Cuniffe (Baker Library), 1990 (Box 32)
    - Dean W. Currie, circa 1982 (Box 32)
    - Arthur R. Cuse (Visiting Consultant), circa 1961 (Box 32)
    - Mary Cutler, circa 1980 (Box 32)
    - Jane M. D'Alessandro, circa 1965 (Box 32)
    - Willard Dalrymple (Health Services), circa 1960 (Box 32)
    - Kristin M. Daly (Research Associate), 1991-1993 (Box 32)
    - John C. Dalton (Health Services), circa 1958 (Box 32)
    - Mary Anne D'Amico, circa 1985 (Box 32)
    - Victor Dana (Executive Education), circa 1975 (Box 32)
    - Lorna M. Daniels (Baker Library), 1960s-1970s (Box 32)
    - Thomas H. Davenport, circa 1990 (Box 32)
    - John Herbert Davis, circa 1956 (Box 32)
    - Joseph R. D'Cruz (Research Associate), circa 1979 (Box 32)
    - Caitlin L. Deinard (HBS Press), 1993 (Box 32)
    - Patricia L. Denault (Business History Review), ca. 1985-circa 1990 (Box 32)
    - Barbara Denning, circa 1975 (Box 32)
    - William DiBartolomeo, circa 1980, (Contact sheet) (Box 32)
    - Douglas Dickson (Harvard Business Review), circa 1985 (Box 32)
    - William J. Dickson (Visiting Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 32)
    - Joshua Dienstag (Research Assistant), circa 1990 (Box 32)
    - John L. DiGaetani, circa 1975-circa 1980 (Box 32)
    - Muriel A. Dilworth (Harvard Business Review), 1979 (Box 32)
    - Phyllis Dininio (Research Assistant), 1986 (Box 32)
    - Samuel H. Donnell, 1950s (Box 32)
    - Billur Dowse (Research Associate), 1988 (Box 32)
    - Frank Dubinskas (Research Associate), 1985 (Box 32)
    - Irene Duffy (MBA Program), 1975 (Box 32)
    - Paula Barker Duffy (HBS Press), circa 1990 (Box 32)
    - John M. Dutton (Research Assistant), circa 1958 (Box 32)
    - John W. Duncan (MBA Program), circa 1973 (Box 32)
    - Thomas W. Dunn, 1960s-1973 (Box 32)
    - Karen Dunn-Haley (Harvard Business Review), 1979 (Box 32)
    - E. Davis Dyer (Harvard Business Review), circa 1990 (Box 32)
    - Helen Eastman, 1940s-1950s (Box 32)
    - Joel W. Eastman (Business History Review), circa 1970 (Box 32)
    - Charles C. Eaton (Baker Library), circa 1921, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Charles C. Eaton (Baker Library), circa 1923 (Box 32)
    - Albert Ross Eckler, 1934 (Box 32)
    - William C. Ellet (HBS Publishing), 1986 (Box 32)
    - Gary Emmons (HBS Bulletin), circa 1985 (Box 32)
    - Bill Endres (Department of Operations) 1987 (Box 32)
    - Gail Epstein, 1985 (Box 32)
    - Judith Esterquest, circa 1975 (Box 32)
    - Anthony Dayton Estes, circa 1980 (Box 32)
    - David W. Ewing (Harvard Business Review), 1960s-1983 (Box 32)
    - Lydia Ewing (Baker Library), circa 1985 (Box 32)
    - William D. Falcon (The Executive), circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - Virginia B. Fales (Harvard Business Review), 1960s (Box 33)
    - Karen E. Feingol (Baker Library), 1960s (Box 33)
    - James S. Feinson (MBA Program), circa 1980 (Box 33)
    - James Fell, 1981 (Box 33)
    - Edward L. Felton, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1971 (Box 33)
    - Dan H. Fenn, Jr. (HBS Bulletin),1967 (Box 33)
    - Mrs. Fenno, 1964 (Box 33)
    - Luke E. Fichthorn, III (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - Lee Field (Research Associate), 1986 (Box 33)
    - Donna H. Feinberg (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 33)
    - John Fieldon (Harvard Business Review), 1959-1961 (Box 33)
    - Hillary Fillios (Finance), circa 1980 (Box 33)
    - Marion Finkle, 1980s (Box 33)
    - Margaret Fish, circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - Laura Fisher (MBA Admissions), 1980s (Box 33)
    - Catherine M. Fitzgerald (Executive Education), circa 1985 (Box 33)
    - Eleanor Fitzpatrick, circa 1970s (Box 33)
    - David Alexander Flash, 1994 (Box 33)
    - Janice Fleischner, circa 1985 (Box 33)
    - Patricia Fleming, 1960s (Box 33)
    - Roberta J. Flexer (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - Ignacio D. Flores, circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - James J. Foley (MBA Program), circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - L. Michael Foley (Office of the Dean), circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - DeFred G. Folts, 1960s (Box 33)
    - Frederick V. Fortmiller (Research Associate), circa 1958 (Box 33)
    - Clifford Alvin Foster (Office of the Dean), circa 1953 (Box 33)
    - Esty Foster, circa 1930 (Box 33)
    - Janet T. Fox, circa 1970 (Box 33)
    - Minnie B. Fox, 1950s (Box 33)
    - James B. Foxworth (Research Associate), circa 1958 (Box 33)
    - Ernest D. Frawley, Publisher (Harvard Business Review), 1960s-1980s (Box 33)
    - Karen Freed (HBS Bulletin), circa 1985 (Box 33)
    - Karen Freeze (Research Associate), 1985 (Box 33)
    - Anne Friedman (Harvard Business Review), circa 1990 (Box 33)
    - Joseph Fromm (Research Assistant), circa 1958 (Box 33)
    - Elmer Newton Funkhouser, Jr. (Office of the Dean), circa 1973 (Box 33)
    - Evonne B. Furey, circa 1985 (Box 33)
    - Frayda Galvin, 1980s (Box 33)
    - Israel Ganot (Research Assistant), 1994 (Box 33)
    - W. Booth Gardner (MBA Program), circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - Caroline F. Williams Gay (Harvard Business Review), circa 1970 (Box 33)
    - Charles N. Gebhard (Case Services), 1960s-1970s (Box 33)
    - Ms. Georgette, circa 1980, (Contact sheet) (Box 33)
    - Pamela M. Germain (External Relations), circa 1985 (Box 33)
    - George W. Gibson (Audio-Visual Aids Division), 1960s (Box 33)
    - Grandon Gill (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 33)
    - Florence "Cash Flo" Glynn (Finance), 1980s (Box 33)
    - Janis Lee Gogan (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 33)
    - Nilgun Gokgur (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 33)
    - Brandt Goldstein (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 33)
    - Sabra Goldstein (Research Assistant), circa 1990 (Box 33)
    - Raymond P. Gomes (Mail and Supply Department), circa 1980 (Box 33)
    - Victoria Good (Executive Education), circa 1985 (Box 33)
    - J. Carey Goodson, circa 1980 (Box 33)
    - Charles I. Gragg, Jr. circa 1970 (Box 33)
    - Irene Granovsky (HBS Publishing), 1993 (Box 33)
    - Hilary Grant (MBA Financial Aid), 1990s (Box 33)
    - Thomas A. Graves, Jr. (Office of the Dean), 1960s (Box 33)
    - Libby Greely, circa 1980 (Box 33)
    - Natalie A. Greenberg (Business History Review), 1985 (Box 33)
    - Ardis Griffin (MBA Program), 1980s (Box 33)
    - Mrs. Grows, 1954 (Box 33)
    - David Gumpert (Harvard Business Review), 1979-1985 (Box 33)
    - Judith Gurney, circa 1980 (Box 33)
    - Isobel J. Haberer (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - Robert Hackett (MBA Program), circa 1980 (Box 33)
    - Patricia C. Hager, circa 1970 (Box 33)
    - Varda Haimo, circa 1980 (Box 33)
    - Chaffee E. Hall, Jr. (MBA Program), 1960s (Box 33)
    - Max R. Hall (Division of Research), circa 1965 (Box 33)
    - Amy L. Halliday (Harvard Business Review), circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Paul Halloran (Operational Support Services), 1989 (Box 34)
    - Charles B. Hamlin (HBS Publishing, 1993) (Box 34)
    - Nancy R. Hammond (Baker Library), circa 1975 (Box 34)
    - Eileen Hankins, circa 1980 (Box 34)
    - Karen E. Hansen (Case Development), circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Jamie Harper (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 34)
    - Bruce E. Harding (Division for Audio-Visual Education), circa 1965 (Box 34)
    - Carolyn Jane Harrigan, circa 1960 (Box 34)
    - T. George Harris, Editor (Harvard Business Review), circa 1980 (Box 34)
    - Sarah S. Hart-Peterson, 1993 (Box 34)
    - Fred Harvey (Baker Library), circa 1980 (Box 34)
    - Edwin Harwood (Harvard Business Review), 1986 (Box 34)
    - Roseann Hassey (MBA Placement Services), circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Patricia F. Hatch (Harvard Business Review), circa 1970 (Box 34)
    - Stephen G. Hayes (Department of Operations), circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Jonathan Headley (Research Assistant), 1993 (Box 34)
    - John L. Henninger (Alumni Relations), 1960 (Box 34)
    - Anita C. Hersum (Office of the Dean), circa 1960 (Box 34)
    - Ruth C. Hetherston, circa 1960 (Box 34)
    - John L. Heyl, 1974 (Box 34)
    - J. Hibbard, circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - Victoria A. Hiebner, circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Mary Jane Higgins (Harvard Business Review), 1990s (Box 34)
    - Takashi Hikino (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - Ramona K. Hilgenkamp (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 34)
    - Shelia Hingorani (Harvard Business Review), circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - Thomas E. Hitchcock (MBA Program), circa 1970 (Box 34)
    - Christine L. Hobart (Harvard-Radcliffe Program in Business Administration), circa 1961 (Box 34)
    - Roderic C. Hodgins (Office of Career Development), 1970s-1980s (Box 34)
    - Anne D. Hodgsdon (Research Assistant), 1975 (Box 34)
    - William Hokanson (Communications), circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - Robert B. Holden (Health Services), circa 1956 (Box 34)
    - Jane Holtz (Research Associate), circa 1978 (Box 34)
    - Helen Honey (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 34)
    - Debra Hoss, 1989-1995 (Box 34)
    - Robert Howard (Harvard Business Review), 1990 (Box 34)
    - Thomas M. Huber, 1993 (Box 34)
    - Lowell H. Hilbert, circa 1940 (Box 34)
    - Joseph E.D. Humphries (Health Services), circa 1965 (Box 34)
    - Eleanor Ann Huser, circa 1980 (Box 34)
    - G. Scott Hutchinson (Harvard Business Review), circa 1975-circa 1980 (Box 34)
    - William O. Ingle (Research Associate), circa 1991 (Box 34)
    - Cynthia H. Ingols (Research Assistant), circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - Ronald E. Jablouski (Research Assistant), circa 1959 (Box 34)
    - Ricardo Jacinto (Research Associate), circa 1986 (Box 34)
    - Arlene Jackson (Baker Library), 1972-1974 (Box 34)
    - Audrey Sullivan Jacob (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - F. Caroline Jacobs (Harvard Business Review), circa 1985-circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - Janice James (Executive Education), circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Ralph James (Executive Education), 1980s (Box 34)
    - William A. Janowsky, (Harvard Business Review) 1970s (Box 34)
    - Eleanor Jaynes, circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Jenness (Finance), circa 1965 (Box 34)
    - Erich Joachimsthaler, 1987, (contact sheets) (Box 34)
    - Richard John (Business History Review), circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - Mary Ann Johnson (Human Resources), circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Elizabeth Wynee Johnson (Research Assistant), 1993 (Box 34)
    - Richard T. Johnson (MBA Program), circa 1965 (Box 34)
    - Frank S. Jones (Office of the Dean), 1960s (Box 34)
    - Robert D. Jones (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 34)
    - Eleanor M. Judd (Baker Library), 1960s (Box 34)
    - Charles A. Judge (MBA Program), circa 1965 (Box 34)
    - Paul R. Judy (Research Assistant), circa 1958 (Box 34)
    - William S. Kaden (Health Services), 1970s (Box 34)
    - Edward M. Kaitz (Research Assistant), circa 1967 (Box 34)
    - William A. Kamins (Research Associate), circa 1957 (Box 34)
    - George Kanaan (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 34)
    - Alan M. Kantrow (Harvard Business Review), 1980s (Box 34)
    - David L. Kapp (Baker Library), 1969 (Box 34)
    - Elizabeth A. M. Karpati (MBA Program), circa 1975-1980s (Box 34)
    - Jane P. Katz (Research Associate), circa 1989 (Box 34)
    - William G. Kaye (Research Assistant), circa 1956 (Box 34)
    - Richard W. Kazmaier (Research Associate), circa 1954 (Box 34)
    - Colleen Keegan (HBS Publishing), 1993 (Box 34)
    - Allen P. Keese (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 34)
    - Barbara A. Kelly, circa 1970 (Box 34)
    - Robert F. Kelly (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 34)
    - Susan Kelly, circa 1985 (Box 34)
    - Robert W. Kent, circa 1988 (Box 34)
    - Timothy Keohane (Custodial Services), circa 1965 (Box 34)
    - Stella A. Kerr (Baker Library), ca. 1940s (Box 34)
    - Marjorie Kierstead (Baker Library), 1978-1985 (Box 35)
    - Bert H. King (MBA Program), circa 1973 (Box 35)
    - Elizabeth King, 1993 (Box 35)
    - Laurence J. Kipp (Baker Library), 1963 (Box 35)
    - Charles A. Kirk (Office of the Dean), 1970s (Box 35)
    - Kate Kirsch, 1986 (Box 35)
    - David B. Kiser (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - Madelyn Kissock (Doctoral Program), circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Sharon F. Kleefield, circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Anne Klein (HBS Fund), 1993 (Box 35)
    - Margaret Virginia Klemme (Baker Library), circa 1962 (Box 35)
    - David Knechle, circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Martin E. Knestrick, circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Rose Kneznek (Bureau of Business Research), circa 1958 (Box 35)
    - David Knights, circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Winifred G. Knopf, circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - John M. Kohlmeier (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Hiroyasu Komine (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 35)
    - Shelley Kooris, circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Helen Kosakowski, 1972 (Box 35)
    - John F. Kosoki (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - David Kotchen, 1991 (Box 35)
    - Rosemarie T. Kowlaski (HBS Publishing), 1992 (Box 35)
    - Julia Kou (Research Assistant), 1993 (Box 35)
    - Robert C. Kramer, circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Pamela Kruh, circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Brenda Kuchinsky (Baker Library), circa 1990 (Box 35)
    - Ronald Kurtz (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Joel Kurtzman (Harvard Business Review), 1993 (Box 35)
    - Barbara B. Kyrillos (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 35)
    - E. Lackowski, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Edward LaCroix, Jr. (Executive Education), circa 1990 (Box 35)
    - Habib Ladjerardi, circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Nancy Lafaytis, circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Gerald F. Lahey (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Frank Lamantea (Baker Library), 1970s (Box 35)
    - Henry W. Lane (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - David Landman, circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - Margaret Lang (MBA Placement), circa 1985 (Box 35)
    - Kristen Langdon (Harvard Business Review), 1993 (Box 35)
    - E. Smith Lanning, circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - Paul Lapointe, circa 1982 (Box 35)
    - Lawrence J. Lasser, circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Florence Bartoshesky Lathrop (Baker Library), 1980s-1993 (Box 35)
    - Eleanor W. Latimer (Research Assistant), circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Carol A. Laucus (Baker Library), circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - Pierre Laurin (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Irving H. LaValle (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - R.L. Lavoie (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Roy Lawrence (Office of the Dean), 1950s (Box 35)
    - Carole Lawton (Doctoral Programs), 1994 (Box 35)
    - Donald H. Layton (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - George Leach, circa 1990 (Box 35)
    - Debbie A. LeClaire (Executive Education), circa 1985 (Box 35)
    - Arthur V. Lee III, circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - James A. Lee (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Diana Lees (Division of Research), 1990s (Box 35)
    - Judith Leff (Research Associate), circa 1985 (Box 35)
    - James A. Leidich (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - George F. Leighton (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - David LeLacheur, 1993 (Box 35)
    - Joel B. Lett (Research Assistant), 1961 (Box 35)
    - James H. Leonhard (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 35)
    - Larry Levine, circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Steven Levy (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - Lucille Lewis (Baker Library), circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Julia Lieblich (Harvard Business Review), 1993 (Box 35)
    - Wendy Faith Liebow (Research Assistant), circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Patricia K. Light, Director (MBA Counseling Services), 1980s (Box 35)
    - Mayer R. Lightdale (Health Services), circa 1975 (Box 35)
    - Grace V. Lindfors (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Maurice M. Lindin (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 35)
    - James S. Lipscomb, circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - George P. Little, 1953 (Box 35)
    - J. Joseph Lowenberg (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Stephanie Logan (HBS Publishing), 1991 (Box 35)
    - Robert Lord (Research Assistant), 1971 (Box 35)
    - Scott D. Lothrop (HBS Fund), circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - Michael L. Lovdal (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 35)
    - Robert W. Lovett (Baker Library), circa 1960-1981 (Box 35)
    - Arnold M. Ludwick (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Craig E. Lundberg (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 35)
    - Herbert L. Lyken (MBA Program), 1969-1970 (Box 35)
    - Jeanne M. Lynch, circa 1975 (Box 35)
    - John Lynch (MBA Program), circa 1980 (Box 35)
    - Richard K. Lynn, circa 1965 (Box 35)
    - Judith Maas (Harvard Business Review), 1980s (Box 36)
    - David J. Macey (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - Elizabeth MacIver (Research Assistant), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Jeanne MacMillan, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Pat Maddox, circa 1985 (Box 36)
    - Scott Mahler (HBS Press), 1992 (Box 36)
    - Phyllis Mahoney (Office of the Dean), circa 1985 (Box 36)
    - Marion Malkasian, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Marie Maliawco, 1990s (Box 36)
    - Kathleen Manion, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Erna Manning (HBS Case Services), 1978 (Box 36)
    - Artemis March, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Liz Markham (MBA Placement Services), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Wesley W. Marple, Jr. (Office of the Dean), circa 1957 (Box 36)
    - Sue Marsh (Baker Library), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Margaret R. Martens, 1993 (Box 36)
    - Samuel A. Martin (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - Deborah Mauger, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Pamela Maus (Research Associate), 1994 (Box 36)
    - Walter C. McBeth, Jr. (Harvard Business Review) (Box 36)
    - Kenneth McCabe (Department of Operations), 1989 (Box 36)
    - Erika M. McCaffrey (Baker Library), circa 1985 (Box 36)
    - Alex McCallum (Harvard Business Review) (Box 36)
    - Allison McCance, circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Charles J. McCarthy (Food Service), 1975 (Box 36)
    - Daniel J. McCarthy (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - Marina McCarthy (Research Assistant), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - William McClements (Research Assistant), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Andrew M. McCosh (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - George E. McCown (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - John A. McCullen (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Kevin McCullough (Research Assistant), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Philip R. McDonald (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - John J. McDonough (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - Duncan C. McDougall (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Robert L. McDowell (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Richard E. McElrath (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - John H. McGavern (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - James McGell (Research Associate), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - J. Timothy McGinley (Office of the Dean), 1965 (Box 36)
    - James A. McGowan, circa 1981 (Box 36)
    - Kathryn McHugh (Executive Education), 1980s (Box 36)
    - James A. McInnes (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Evelyn Jean McIntyre (Baker Library), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - R. Bruce McKern (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Robert B. McKersie (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - Marjorie McLaughlin (Audio-Visual Department), ca. 1970 (Box 36)
    - Ruth McMullen, President (HBS Publishing), 1993 (Box 36)
    - Elizabeth H. McNair (Research Associate), 1990s (Box 36)
    - Leslie McNamara, circa 1985 (Box 36)
    - Robert Andrew McNearney (Research Assistant), circa 1953 (Box 36)
    - David L. McNeil, circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Franklin R. Madera (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Maureen Malin (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Joseph R. Mancuso (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Victor L. Marma (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Albert G. Mather, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Philip D. Matthews (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - William E. Matthews (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Richard Melnick (Research Assistant), circa 1992 (Box 36)
    - Morris Mendelson (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - Lucia M. Menzer (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 36)
    - Glenn W. Merry (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 36)
    - Gale D. Merseth, circa 1973 (Box 36)
    - B. Robert F. Meyer (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - Paul Meyers, circa 1985 (Box 36)
    - Tom Michalak (Baker Library), 2001 (Box 36)
    - Caroline Michel (Division Research), circa 1985 (Box 36)
    - Anna M. Miller (Case Services), 1978 (Box 36)
    - Arlene Miller (MBA Counseling Services), circa 1985 (Box 36)
    - John A. Miller (Harvard Business Review), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Lisa Miller (Harvard Business Review), circa 1985 (Box 36)
    - Richard Miller (Research Associate), circa 1975 (Box 36)
    - M. Ashley Miller-Crosier, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - William Mini (Facilities Maintenance), 1980s (Box 36)
    - Jan-Erik Modig (Research Assistant), circa 1972 (Box 36)
    - Charles B. Moffett (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - E. Robert Moline (MBA Program Technology), 1994 (Box 36)